

#### **CONTACT**

- **J** +91-9049963060
- 🔀 aksbaylilani60@gmail.com
- Ulhasnagar, Maharashtra
- Portfolio
- AkshaykumarLilani
- in akshay-lilani

#### **EDUCATION**

# Part Time Full Stack Web Developer Course

Masai School 03/2023 - 12/2023

# Bachelor of Engineering (Information Technology)

Vivekanand Education Society's Institute of Technology 2014 - 2018

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript | Express.js | RESTful APIs |
HTML5 | React | Node.js | CSS3 |
MongoDB

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Problem Solving | Time Management | Documentation

#### **INTERESTS**

 Stock Market (Technical Analysis -Equities)

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022

## Akshaykumar Lilani

#### **Full Stack Web Developer**

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Versatile Full Stack Web Developer with more than a year of experience in MERN, Django REST Framework, Docker, Python Scripting, Node Scripting, PineScript, AWS EC2, AWS S3, and Salesforce REST APIs. Proven track record in solo and collaborative projects, showcasing technical versatility, problem-solving, and effective teamwork.

#### **PROJECTS**

### 1. OnlineBicycleShop | 🌐 | 🍞

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | JSON Web Server

- Built a bicycle shopping website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript on the frontend
- Implemented filtering, sorting, and searching functionality
- Utilized JSON Server as the backend to handle API requests

### 2. LetsCamp | 🌐 | 🍙

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | EJS |

- Developed a full-stack campgrounds booking project using MongoDB, Express, and EJS
- · Implemented user authentication and permissions
- Utilized Mapbox to display campgrounds on a map

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Teson LLP**

Senior Software Engineer

Sept 2022 - Present

#### Job responsibilities:

- Creating user-friendly website parts with React for a great experience.
- Designing strong databases to keep our apps running smoothly.
- Contributing to API development for better communication between different parts of our system.
- Leading React version updates to keep our apps performing well.
- Deploying websites reliably for a seamless online experience.
- Integrating secure payment methods for smooth transactions.
- Improving website speed for a better user experience.

#### **Accenture Solutions Private Limited**

**Application Development Associate** 

Oct 2018 - Aug 2019

#### Job responsibilities:

- Monitored vast data from Digital Meters in Oracle Utilities
   MDM for a major US Utilities client, ensuring accuracy.
- Produced weekly Excel reports, using SQL and SSRS for indepth analysis, aiding strategic decision-making.